as well as radiant and keeping track of
corporations which i think is done
mainly in our product app but that could
be its own thing I guess let's write and
keep track of corporations but this one
was actually going to be about radiant
and keeping track of nonprofits so
people that we donate money to what is
their mission where is the money going
where is it coming from I do believe
that there's a TED talk talking about
nonprofits and how we do need to pay the
CEOs more and not be so concerned about
the money going to top-rated talent
because you want top-rated talent
especially in the nonprofit fields and I
would agree with that but I also think
that spending a million dollars on a
gala that raises 1.1 million is maybe
ridiculous and so especially if you're
not actually following your mandate and
I give money in the Red Cross for Haiti
relief after they have a disaster how
much is going to there and what are they
actually doing I would like to be able
to keep track of that and so a nonprofit
and charity ratings up would be very
helpful